对于每一种动能
都有大小相等、方向相反的反作用力
北极圈
致命螳螂
翻译制作anthrax06
雷达的设计，是为了保护我们免受攻击
雷达站建立在山顶上
在荒漠中，在杳无人烟的森林深处
更多的，是建立在保密和隔绝的地方
在两大洋的上空有雷达巡逻机
在大洋之中，人造岛屿雷达站保护着我们的侧翼
这是近海警戒船
数百海里外的它们正在担负海上警戒任务
还有一张雷达网横跨未设防的
美国与加拿大的边界
一条松树雷达网
除此之外
还有另外一条侦查网络
加拿大中部雷达网
甚至再往北，在靠近北极圈的位置
还有一道被称为DEW的远程雷达预警系统
随时准备着，对在极地地区发生的偷袭首先发出警告信号
DEW远程预警舰队已经组建
自从诺曼底战役以来
它们执行了大多数大型的和秘密的军事行动
它们驰骋在广袤的极地冰海之中
义无反顾的同漫长的时间和恶劣的天气做着斗争
船上卸下堆积成山的补给品，以及大量的
供冰上作业的设备、车辆和人员
首先，平整出供大型运输机起降的飞机场
然后修建营房、机库和指挥所
在一些人忙着铺设输油管道的同时
另一些工程坦克正在建设储油仓库
工作在日以继夜、昼夜不停
一周无休的进行着
终于，船队开走了，夏天也过去了
但是工程完工了
在人类探索北极一百周年的时候，红鹰一号
DEW远程雷达预警网的重要枢纽
正式投入使用
Parkman上校抵达，派出吉普车接机
Parkman上校?欢迎你到这来
更北边的
大陆顶端
是DEW网的前哨站
嘿Mike,嘿Mike,来看看这个
我什么也没看到
嘿，等一下
你听!
这声音好像就在我们头顶!
这里是Kane,7327号巡逻机，呼叫红鹰一号
红鹰一号请回答
你好7327，这里是红鹰一号，收到你的来电，完毕
Pete，能帮我接一下老头子吗?
好的，收到
长官，Kane中尉有事找你
我是Parkman上校, Walter?有什么事？
长官，我们在气象四号上空
哨站遭到毁坏，看来像是屋顶塌了
如果里面有人的话肯定受伤了，甚至更糟
我试着联系他们，可是没有收到回话，完毕
我们这就过去!通话结束
气象四号最后一次报告是在什么时候?
是在八点钟，长官，准确无误
- 看你能不能联系上他们
- 好的
红鹰一号呼叫气象四号,
红鹰一号呼叫气象四号，请回答
没有回应，长官
再试试
红鹰一号呼叫气象四号,
红鹰一号呼叫气象四号，请回答
调度室，我是Parkman上校
把我的飞机准备好
还有，叫上Pizar中尉
红鹰一号呼叫气象四号
红鹰一号呼叫气象四号，请回答
两个人就这样不见了!
是啊
我不明白
当他们在八点钟报告的时候一切都正常
从那以后也没有什么反常情况的报告，没有暴风雪。。
这屋子不是被风刮倒的
像是有什么东西从屋顶掉了进来把墙砸塌了
如果是一架飞机的话。。
也许，这里发生的事并没有什么特殊的原因
也许他们现在正在回基地的路上
步行吗?
那他们也会留下脚印的，你看到了吗?
来看看这个!
你发现什么了?
我不知道!
- 是飞机吗?
- 没有一架飞机能滑行那么短
直升机?
不是，直升机不会留下这样的痕迹
如果这里发生的事不是因为什么特殊的原因，那。。
我可不会打这个赌的
那么，你最近一起与气象站联系
是在五天前直升机
给那里运送补给的时候?
是的，长官
- 你查过气象一号了吗?
- 是的
气象四号在八点十三的时候和他们联系过
一切都很正常!
我发现了些东西上校，但不知道是什么
我从来没有见过这样的信号
它在那，它又不见了!
嘿，它又出现了, 你认为这是什么？
我可不想冒任何险，拉响红色警报!
航向360，高度三千英尺，不明飞行物距离九十英里
红色领队呼叫塔台
什么也没有发现，请给我们提供新的航向
不明飞行消失，返回本部
Jerry!
飞糖呼叫红鹰一号
红鹰一号请回答
你好飞糖，这里是红鹰一号，请讲
红鹰一号，我们正在C47残骸上空
他们找到它了，上校!
- 找到他们的位置
- 是的，长官
- 通知Pizar中尉
上校!
看起来和气象站那一样
没错
他们在哪?尸体在哪?
别着急
小心!
这究竟是什么。。
这是什么?
我不知道
看起来像是从什么东西上折断的
头上就像针一样尖利
我看不出来，你难到我了
我们怎么办?
我们必须得通知CONAD
这里是CONAD
美国本土防空司令部
位于科罗拉多斯普林斯市
他们的工作重点是拱卫北美大陆领空的安全
他们工作的成败事关数百万美国人的
生与死
这些是热线电话!
使用这些电话，只要十五秒就能联通阿拉斯加
只要十秒就能给纽芬兰发去警报
五秒可以联系到各位!
三秒就能联系到五角大楼指挥部
我是Ford将军
是的
我知道了
好的，我会坐飞机过去
北方司令部的东西运到了
下午好先生们
我是Ford将军，哦，没关系的，请坐吧
先生们
我知道空军方面没有给你们太多时间让你们进行研究
而且在这么短的时间里，要把它完全搞清楚
也确实是有难度的
但是国防部希望
在接下来的两天里，你们要全力以赴，对这个东西
能够得出一些结论
Gunther教授，我想你应该是这里的负责人
我们所有人达成了一个共识
这样东西是从某种生物身上掉落下来的
但这个东西作为这个生物的一部分，它到底是什么
我们完全摸不着头绪
我们的物种学家Arnold Burton博士
也无法确定它的来源
Harvy Pierce教授通过他的研究确信
这个钩子状的东西，肯定不属于神经系统
看起来你们似乎还是搞不清这是个什么东西
你说的很正确，将军
先生们，让我们来梳理一下
刚才你们告诉这个钩子状的物体
是来自某种生物体，对吧
但这个东西不是军方的货物
而且在飞机起飞时它也并不在飞机上
所以它一定是在撞机之后掉落的，对吗?
听起来合乎逻辑
那我们面前的这个东西到底是什么?
这应该没有那么困难，你们知道北极没有多少种动物
这个我们也想到了，将军
你不会是想说这个东西所属的那个生物
是一个未知物种？
有这种可能性，我们建议你进行调查，将军
怎么做?
我们建议你去找一下华盛顿自然历史博物馆的
Nedrick Jackson博士来看一下这个东西
他是那里的首席科学家
和我国在食肉动物研究方面的权威
你把我说糊涂了，教授
他专门处理生活在远古地质时期的
动物和植物的化石
他只需要用少量的骨骼
就能够复原
史前生物
- 嗨Marge
- 嗨
你在做什么?
一个孩子在初中科学兴趣小组上做的
甚至还增加了一组额外的脊椎骨，就像它还不够多似的
给你，你想数数吗?
听我说，如果我还想让下个月的杂志出版发行的话
我们最好开始工作了
我拿了一些图片
穿越时代的生命之旅
展现史前生物的演化进程
从深海水母，到恐龙，再到原始人
听起来很好
而且我打算加入一些上次野外考察拍的照片
那真是太好了
哦，抱歉
我是Jackson
五角大楼?好的，我会等的
你知道嘛也许他们想重新招我回去服役
我是Jackson博士
Ford将军?
是的
我明白将军
好的将军，我马上就赶过去
没什么事吧?
当然
是不是每天五角大楼都打电话找你
- 你可真是好打听
- 好吧，故弄玄虚
如果告诉你，你能保密吗
我保证!
他们在北极发现了一个古老的生物骨骼
五角大楼想知道那骨骼是属于哪种生物的
这看起来不像是骨头
更像是软骨或某种组织
如此巨大的结构一定有
其非常特殊的用途从而便于卡特尔化
你知道它是属于哪种生物的吗?
不，不知道
如果它是骨头的话我们肯定能查出来
然而不管它是什么，它肯定不是来自一只动物身上
因为每种我们已知的动物物种都有骨骼结构
事实上，爬行动物和人类都有
甚至鸟类也有
看起来我们快无计可施了
相反，我们取得了很大的进展
至少我们知道了它不是骨头
这样能引导我们最终查出它到底是什么
那有什么生物是没有骨骼结构的吗?
那就多了，蠕虫、昆虫、蜗牛、贝壳类生物
一些无脊椎动物它们的骨骼在身体之外
它们的外壳就是骨骼
非常坚硬，足以保护体内器官
昆虫在它们的头和身体上有一些柔软灵活的地方
从而便于它们自由的活动
它们身上一些褶皱的位置是由肌肉相连接
这很有可能就是
那是一只虫子?
这就是引导我们使用排除法的过程
当然，如果它是一只虫子
它绝对不会告诉我们它究竟是什么
我们只能靠现有的这部分去寻找答案
但更多的只能依靠推论
博士，你的话听起来有点像是福尔摩斯
有一点
Gunther教授, 从这个钩状物根部流出的液体
- 你进行化验了吗?
- 我们做了，当时能做的我们都做了
当然，你们也不知道到底应该找什么
没错
我对昆虫学并不是十分了解，但我似乎记得。。
除极少数外，大多数昆虫的血液中
是不含有红血球的
现在我们怀疑这个东西可能是来自一只昆虫
你能帮我对这些液体进行一下化验然后把结果告诉我吗?
- 我很乐意
- 谢谢
好了将军，关于这个东西
Gunther教授会进行化验，然后。。
我们就会知道我们所想的到底是什么
你觉得我们会有所发现吗?
我们会尽最大努力的
极地悲剧被披露
空军公开了一起神秘的事故和失踪事件
那么，那就是他们把你找去的原因了
别跟我兜圈子了，Ned Jackson
我很抱歉
有句老话说的好，不要想着对媒体有任何隐瞒
即使是我这种只负责一本博物馆刊物的人
也不会失去对新闻的敏感
事情就是这样
- 也许吧
- 我知道!
- 你也许不知道!
- 这就是明摆着的嘛!
听我说
五角大楼以前从来没有找你咨询过
报纸上说他们掌握着一个秘密
一加一等于二，所以接下来
他们必须要知道一些你的研究领域的情况
哦Ned, 跟我说说吧
你不知道那意味着什么，如果我可以
把一个发生在本世纪的故事刊登出来的话!
我。。
- 他们没有说那是保密的
- 你知道?
好吧，就像报纸上说的那样
那里确实发生了坠机和失踪事件
但故事的关键是，他们在上次坠机中找到的东西
它，它大约有五英尺长
它的外表是绿色的
可能是从某种生物的身体上折断的
你在说什么
那东西是活的
那东西一定是巨大的令人难以置信
我认为那东西来自一只昆虫身上
一只昆虫?
我画给你看
即使尺寸缩小了可看上还是很吓人，是不是?
不，不会的
它看起来就是一直蚱蜢或是蟋蟀腿上的刺
蚱蜢和蟋蟀可并不吃肉
已经至少有五个人失踪了
如果它是昆虫身上的
那它一定是有史以来最大的生物
你确定你没事吧?
在雪地里有很长的像刹车印一样的痕迹
仿佛那个东西是从天而降
我是Jackson
哦你好，Gunther教授，有结果了吗
我明白先生，谢谢
他们刚刚做完了血液化验
没有红血球
它就是来自一只昆虫身上
这只琥珀里的蚂蚁已经有九千万岁了
现在我们已经能够从这样的琥珀标本中学到很多知识
某些古代昆虫直至今天它的外形都没有发生改变
另外一些为了满足不断变化的生存条件
而不得不改变自己的外形
还有一些种类则彻底灭绝了
我只是不能相信像你所说的竟然存在这么大的昆虫
看看你身后的墙上，教授
这只史前的蜻蜓根据测量它的翼展能达到两英尺长
而且它的外表和现在的蜻蜓很相似
它也是肉食性昆虫
没错，它是很大，但也只有两英尺
这就是你所说的巨型昆虫吗?
我可从来没说过我们要找的是一只蜻蜓
那你认为它是什么?
老实跟你说，我也不是很确定
你是一名病理学家Gunther教授
病理学的领域是有限的
但古生物学中我们真正探明的领域也很有限
反之，我们就是要尽量将
我们的视野放宽要包罗万象
好吧，只是为了进行探讨
我们承认曾经存在过这样的昆虫
那它怎么能活到今天?
没错! 即使最近在西伯利亚发现的
那些史前动物，它们也都是死的
尽管它们的肉能吃
它们的皮还能做衣服
象牙还能制成工具
但那些猛犸象被发现时已经死了
你确定它们死了吗?
什么意思?每个人都知道它们死了
每个人都说它们死了
假设那些当地人没有急着把它们切成肉块
假设它们在冰里被发现时还活着
你这位有学识的朋友总是喜欢这样吗?
好吧，教授
你我都清楚，如果一个活的有机体
被以极快的速度冷冻住
理论上讲可能会阻止其
原生细胞改变几何图形
会永远保持死时的状态
理论上讲，是的
那你自己想想这是不合理的吗？
是否那些猛犸象在那段时间里可能还活着
只是它们还没有来得及融化和复活
就被那些西伯利亚人给杀了!
你。。你相信这些吗?
我相信!
而且我坚信这一点，除非有人能讲出更好的理论
听着，五个人失踪了
他们死了，就这样不见了
一点踪迹都没有留下!
只能是被某种食肉生物吃了!
但是有很多昆虫都是以吃其它种类的昆虫为生
你从哪入手呢?
想想那个钩子
把它想象的非常非常小
把它想象成我们今天已知的那些昆虫的一部分
像蚱蜢、甲虫或是蟋蟀
那你再想想
在普通的食肉昆虫中，哪种会有这样的钩子?
Ned, 你做的都是假设
每一个古生物学家都会这样做
看啊，先是下颚骨，然后是牙齿
不管它们是吃肉的还是食草的，你都从那开始想!
一只普通的昆虫，还是食肉的
我想到了一个!
它的食物主要是小昆虫
例如叶蝉、草蜢、毛虫等
很大一部分食物可能还包括小青蛙和蜥蜴
雌性要比雄性体积大很多
当交配完之后，雌性会杀死它的伴侣
这个钩子是他们在飞机上找到的
很有可能是它前腿上的刺
如果这就是我们要找的巨型生物的话。。
我会是否有什么东西能够杀死它
它的毁灭力远远超过它的外表
它能走，会跳还会飞
它的胃口永远不知道满足
你是说，是这个可爱的小虫子?
是的，那个可爱的小虫子
这地球的生物的当中
再没有比这更贪婪更致命的生物了
那就是掠食螳螂
格陵兰岛的爱斯基摩人陷入恐慌
有什么新发生的灾祸吗, 将军?
没有了，先生吗
嘿，你是不是自然历史博物馆的Jackson博士?
- 没错
- 你为什么被叫来?
- Jackson博士是我的老朋友了
- 这不是真正的原因,将军
你是一个古生物学家，这是不是超出你的研究范围了?
你还有什么理论吗，Jackson博士?
先生们, 如果你们处在我的位置
你们所说的理论，那不是事实，只是一种推测
我相信你们对那些猜测不会乱写
因为那可能是灾难性的
我们相信你们已经意识到了
希望你们能跟我们合作从而避免民众的过度恐慌
我知道我可以相信你们的
祝你好运Ned
谢谢，我会尽力的
- 嗨!
- 准备好了吗?
就差把它扣上了
我告诉了空军方面不喜欢等人
我这就好了，给你，干点你力所能及的
很高兴你能来送我
我也这样想
你知道嘛，北极是我唯一没有研究过的地方
那些也是我的吗?
不，博士，那些是我的
你的?
你不能光自己去而把你的摄影师丢下，是不是?
我的什么?
我给Ford将军打了电话
请求批准我作为你的摄影师和你一起去
我想他忘了告诉你了
小伙计，这次真的要写成一篇故事了
你为了这个故事早就做好准备了，是不是?
差不多吧
走吧!
上校
Jackson博士从华盛顿过来了，他带了。。
我是说。。
- 我们。。
- 说清楚点!
他和一个女人一起来的
一个女人
I thought they'd stopped
making them.
Then show them in.
是的，长官
I'm Ned Jackson Colonel,
I'm sure that Washington...
Excuse me, this is Miss Marjorie Blain;
Colonel Joe Parkman.
El General Ford sent me up.
I'm magazine editor for the
Museum of Natural History.
How do you do?
Uh, that will be all men.
It looks like you don't have
too many women up here Colonel.
Ah we have a little joke up here...
The boys say there's a girl
behind every tree.
Only try and find a tree.
Well when do we see what
we came for.
I'll have a plane any
time you're ready.
I'm ready.
Fine.
These are the skid marks.
At least what's left of them.
We found the same marks at the
weather shack, and the Eskimo village.
Here Colonel.
Got it?
Eight and a half feet.
Let's get back to the plane.
At ease.
Gentlemen, this is
Marjorie Blaine.
I thought you wouldn't mind too much if
she had a look around your recreation room.
Aw she's like a butterfly.
Light and crosses
absolutely boss.
Yes Corporal?
Well, ah, with your permission
sir...
Would it be alright if...
would it be alright if...
I asked Miss Blaine to dance, sir?
Corporal that decision is entirely
up to Miss Blaine.
Yes sir.
Miss Blaine would you care to...
Well, what I mean
is... while I'm not...
yes Corporal I'd love to.
Oh hi. Hi.
Hi Ned.
Thought you were going to
join us.
Ah I've been busy. You two
run along, have fun.
What are you up to?
I'm trying to find out
how big this thing is.
You know, people used to think that
carnivorous plants were the funk.
Actually there are about 450
species of them.
Some are almost 6 feet tall.
I'm convinced that we're
dealing with a Mantis and...
whose geological world the smallest
insects were as large as man.
And, the failing to find those insects
for its food, it's...
Well it's, doing the best
it can.
If there is such a thing why
hasn't anybody seen it?
Well those who have are dead!
Ah, who can be sure?
It may have been locked in a
prison of ice millions of years ago.
Well what could have released
it after all that time?
Oh, any sort of unusual vibration,
You know how, mountain climbers
are afraid of thunder?
Well, it's because the sound of the
vibration may start an avalanche.
Hit the alert button!
Yes sir!
Operations! Colonel Parkman speaking...
Condition Red! Scramble
all aircraft immediately!
Condition Red!
Coffee Colonel?
Nine hours and not a whisper.
Which is alright with me.
Red Eagle One, this is Otter 4
Hello Otter 4, this is
Red Eagle One, go ahead.
We have nothing here. Request
permission to return to base. Over.
Request denied, continue search
procedure. Over and out.
The only thing to do is
to keep the patrols out
straight around the
clock until we're sure.
And remember, I want a report on
anything from Mid Canada, or Pine tree.
Anything. You understand?
Yes sir.
Got the Mid Canada Radar Fence
on the line sir.
This is Colonel Parkman.
Oh Colonel, Blue Captain Hawkins, here.
This is just a stab in the dark...
but you chaps asked us to report
anything unusual and...
yes...
As I said, it may not mean a thing,
but we caught an unidentified object
in our scope.
Could have been a storm
or a weather balloon.
It was a faint signal that
came a West.
But it might be that oversized
bug of yours?
What time was it?
Early. Zero four hundred
I suspect.
Thanks Hawkins.
Thanks very much.
Zero four hundred, that's almost six
hours after he left here.
Now it's 1500 miles to
the Mid Canada line.
Oh that's no good he'd have to
be doing better than 200 miles an hour.
Why not Joe?
We're dealing with an insect.
The deer fly does 600 an hour!
Well that's almost as fast
as a jet!
The Mid Canada line is 1500 miles
South of here, right?
Right.
And, where was that
Weather shack 4?
Right there, straight on
the eightieth meridian.
And the, and the C47
crash was here.
That's right, due South
of the Weather shack.
What are you getting at Ned?
And the Eskimo village?
Right there, between us and the C47.
Hey wait a minute.
He's been going straight South!
And he'll keep going South
till he reaches the tropics...
where he'll find the
same kind of climate
and jungle vegetation from
which he came originally.
Now let's see he'll probably
pass over...
Labrador, Nova Scotia, then
he'll hit the Gulf Stream.
And I'm sure the warm air above
the Gulf Stream will attract him
and he'll follow it all the
way down to South America.
I've got CONAD on the
hot line Colonel.
They say it's important.
Thanks.
This is Colonel Parkman.
Are you sure?
Thanks.
Pine Tree got it too.
It went through Newfoundland.
Well it looks like we're
on our way to Washington.
Come on Marge.
Grab your toothbrush.
"MANTIS REPORTED AT BANGOR"
"AIR FORCE ALERTED!"
"CURFEW ORDERED IN NEW ORLEANS!"
"Fear of Mantis Mounting"
"CONGRESSMAN CALLS MANTIS HOAX"
"DEMANDS INVESTIGATION"
All over the United States this morning...
Some 400,000 members, of the civilian
ground observer corp...
are gathered to learn more about
this fantastic creature.
This program is being presented by the
Continental Air Defense Command.
Our first speaker is Major
General Mark Ford.
- General Ford.
Thank you.
I want to say at the outset...
That contrary to rumor, and certain
newspaper headlines,
the so called deadly Mantis is no
imaginary scare.
It's a very real and,
present danger.
With me this morning is
Colonel Parkman.
Commanding officer of an advanced radar
interceptor base deep in the Arctic Circle.
Colonel Parkman.
Thank you sir.
Ladies and Gentlemen...
I saw this creature attack our base.
I visited the weather shack,
and I also inspected the
wreckage of the aircraft
that this thing destroyed.
Now we have every reason to believe
that the Mantis is flying South...
Along the Gulf Stream.
And we believe that it will be one you
devoted men and women...
of the Civilian Ground
Observer Corp...
who will spot it next time it appears.
I have with me today
Dr. Nedrick Jackson...
Curator of the department of Paleontology
at the Museum of Natural History.
Dr. Jackson has something important
to show you.
Doctor.
Gentlemen.
Thank you.
This object, is a spur
broken off the fore
leg of the Mantis when
it destroyed the C47.
Now the spur of a normal size Mantis
is so small it's difficult to measure.
This spur, as you can see,
is nearly 5 feet long...
which will give you some
idea as to the creature's size.
Thank you, doctor.
Now you ground observers are well
trained in the identification of aircraft.
Here, to scale, is
the deadly Mantis,
and here, is the C47,
which it destroyed.
One other thing.
You spotters should listen
for a loud droning sound,
much like that of a squadron of
heavy bombers flying in formation.
Now the Coast Guard and the Navy
have been alerted and are standing by...
On the Eastern seaboard.
If the Mantis is sited the procedure
will be the same as though...
an enemy aircraft
had been spotted.
Take no chances. Report any
unusual flying objects.
Thank you.
Target is down!
Cannot confirm kill, due
to low overcast.
Returning to Carrier.
Out.
Well, here comes another one.
Granary fire in Minneapolis.
Minneapolis not a stir.
There's some power lines
down near Richmond.
Richmond Virginia?
Yeah.
There's some birds flying in Fresno.
Fresno, Fresno...
Oh, I'm so tired.
Where is Fresno?
California?
Fresno, California.
Hi.
Hi Marge.
Hello. Ned.
Hey, what are you up to?
Well, it's kind of a private deal.
We call it operation Marge
because she dreamed it up. Oh?
We're charting every unusual
occurrence in the country.
Some may have been caused by the
Mantis. This might give us a clue.
Any luck? Well they're too
scattered to mean anything yet.
You kids know what time it is.
It's after midnight.
Now you're dismissed,
both of you... But General I have the...
No "buts" about it. You heard
what the General said.
Your going straight home
young lady.
And I'm the guy whose taking you.
Night Ned.
Goodnight Marge.
< We interrupt this program
to bring you a news flash >
< A train wreck has been reported north
of Laurel, Maryland, on U.S. highway one. >
< The Engine and 5
cars were overturned
in what appears to have
been a freak accident. >
< We will bring you further details
as they come in. >
It's only a few miles from here.
We'll have a look.
Sorry Colonel, been a train wreck.
You'll have to back to Warrington road.
Take the detour to your left, to Laurel.
Pretty bad?
Could have been a lot worse.
How'd it happen?
Probably couldn't see the warning
in the fog.
Can't tell for sure. The
Engineer is still unconscious.
Joe do you think it might...
No.
It's just an accident.
Come on. Let's go.
Gracias.
The light just turned green.
It's too dangerous to
drive in fog like this.
Remember what happened to
that train back there.
M-m-m, this is more
dangerous.
We better get going.
Oh, you forgot your package lady!
Thank you driver.
You know, it's good to get home safely...
with all these strange things
going on around here.
Oh there's nothing to worry about 'mam.
You just be careful out in that fog.
Thank you.
< An inter urban bus
was demolished at the
intersection of Forbin
Avenue and Arlington Road. >
< The cause of the
accident, which occurred
only 5 minutes ago is still
to be explained... >
<... since there was no other vehicle
involved. >
< This accident, in
addition to the train wreck
which was reported a very
short time before... >
<... makes a total of 7 accidents in
this area within the last 24 hours. >
Take it easy! How about a couple
of blankets up here.
What happened?
Haven't got any idea Colonel. Something
must have lifted the bus and smashed it.
The front end's okay so
we know it didn't run into anything.
You boys might just as well go back.
There aren't any bodies!
Oh say, take care of this
lady for me, will you please.
Attention, all military and civil
defense personnel.
Attention, all police and fire
department personnel.
The Mantis has been
sighted over Washington!
I repeat. The Mantis has been sited
over Washington.
Let's go.
Excuse me, pardon...
This is a general alert!
ANDREWS AIR FORCE BASE
ANACOSTIA, D. C.
Archer this is Beagle One Seven.
Airborne with 4 chickens
heading zero three five. Over.
It's Colonel Parkman, sir.
Beagle One Seven, Archer control...
Continue on your present heading...
bogey at 12 o'clock, 100 miles.
Maintain present air speed...
Altitude at five thousand, Over.
Bogey tracking one five zero.
I've got Baltimore, General.
Go ahead Baltimore.
Second plot three four zero,
Range, one five zero.
Un identified object.
Speed: 250,
Altitude: 2000.
Dropping fast.
Dixie three five bravo,
Range: 150
Speed: 250
Altitude now: 2000
Dropping fast.
It's still moving Northeast.
You think you'll be able
to drive it out to sea?
I hope so.
Air Defense Warning Red!
Stand by to lock on.
Baltimore, warning red.
Philadelphia, warning red.
I repeat, red.
Attention Missile field:
warning red.
Pass to all gun sites.
Guns free, fire at any object
not identified as friendly.
I repeat, pass to all
gun sites...
Guns free, fire at any object not
identified as friendly.
Dixie 35 Bravo, 342 Range 110.
Victor 25 Victor, 352 range 110.
Victor 25 Victor, contact lost.
Victor 25 Victor, Contact lost.
Dixie 35 Bravo, contact lost.
What happened?
He dropped below the radar net.
Well does that mean you've lost it?
One of the ground observers will
pick it up.
This is one nine hotel.
Bogey range...
Flying East. This is one nine hotel...
Thank you.
Initial track, bravo golf, zero three
three nine, at two five. going Northeast.
Eagle one seven, Archer control.
Vector one niner zero. bogey at 12 o'clock.
Steady on course, twenty miles, over.
That'll put it over
Newark in a few minutes.
Archer, this is Beagle One Seven.
When steady
on vector, bogey will be 12 o'clock.
Archer control, this is Beagle One Seven.
We've splashed Mantis.
Give me pigeons to home plate.
Hey Clark! They said on television that
the flyer who shot him down...
is going in the tunnel
after him.
Did you see it crawl into
the tunnel?
Hey bud!
Hey, hey bud! Bud! Hey!
Hey bud,
is it still in the tunnel?
It ain't out here Mac!
Anybody killed?
I only know what I read
in the papers!
Hey smart guy, I thought I told you
to stay out of that road, now come on...
get back there! " I'm going
home and watch it on TV."
Why go ahead home
and watch it on TV.
Alright, don't push! " I'll
push..." I see anything anyway
Yeah, tell it to your
neighbor will ya!
That's all the smoke we need.
Shut it off!
How much longer do you
think it'll take?
Well we got about a 90 percent
saturation of smoke in the tunnel now!
I don't think we can
do any better, General.
We'll be lucky if we can
hold what we've got.
Those wet tarpaulins will hold
the smoke alright.
Just keep pumping!
Everything's under control
on the Jersey side sir.
What about the smoke?
It's packed in solid
the tarp's holding it fine.
Did you go inside?
Yes sir, but we didn't get too close.
How far in do you estimate it to be?
Oh I'd ah, I'd say, about
a quarter of a mile from this end.
That puts the Mantis
below the water line.
I don't think we ought
to wait much longer, sir.
What do you think Ned?
It's no question in my mind that
he's mortally wounded.
If we can keep him in that
tunnel he'll die!
Is there anything between us
and the Mantis on this end?
17 cars, according to
the automatic counter.
If he breaks through those tunnel
walls we'll have a flood on our hands.
What do you say, General?
Go ahead, Joe.
Good luck Joe.
Alright men.
You've all been told what to do.
Now the purpose of that smoke
in there is to give us cover.
Use it! Now which of you
men is carrying the chemical mines?
Stay up front with me!
And remember, those 3-R-G mines are
effective only in a limited area.
So watch for my signal
before you throw them.
Alright men, Take Masks!
Let's go!
There's your cover for next months
magazine, Marge.
Well go on, take your picture.
Would you mind telling me
what's so funny Colonel?
Who me?
Well nothing at all.
Can I help you with
the Camera? No thanks.
Exactly where did you
crash into him, Joe?
Well, just about center
of the right hand side.
If you follow me, I'll show you.
There. I think you can
see right there, sir.
It's at the uh,
base of the neck.
Ned what do you call...
Look out Marge!
I thought you said
you killed him?
Don't blame Joe, that was an
auto-reflex mechanism, it's dead alright.
Here, put me down.
I said, put me down!
What's the matter?
Don't you like it up here?
I've got pictures to take!
Well, that can wait.
This is no place for romance
Joe Parkman.
What about my pictures?
Let Ned do it.
Ha, ha, ha, ha...